Guide to the Archives of Industrial Society (AIS) Information Files, ca. 1890s-present AIS.Info.Files
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- G
  - Greek Orthodox Church; SEE Orthodoxos Ekklesia tes Hellados
  - Group Against Smog and Pollution; SEE GASP (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Grubstake, Inc.
  - Guardian Angels (Organization). Pittsburgh Chapter
  - Guardian Angels Roman Catholic Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Gulf Building (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Gulf Oil Corporation
  - Gumbert Industrial School for Girls (McCandless, Pa.)
  - Gumbert School for Girls; SEE Gumbert Industrial School for Girls (McCandless, Pa.)
- H
  - H. H. Robertson Company
  - H. J. Heinz Company
  - H. Obernauer & Co.; SEE Obernauer & Co.
  - Hall, Gus
  - Hamschuld, Joseph
  - Hartwood (Fox Chapel, Pa.)
  - Hartwood Acres (Fox Chapel, Pa.); SEE Hartwood (Fox Chapel, Pa.)
  - Hazelwood (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Health and Welfare Federation of Allegheny County. Bureau of Community Councils
  - Hebrew Bakers' Union. Local 44; SEE Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America. Local 44 (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Hebrew Free Loan Association of Pittsburgh (Pa.)
  - Hebrew Institute of Pittsburgh
  - Heinz Company; SEE H. J. Heinz Company
  - Heinz, H. John (Senator)
  - Hemphill Family
  - Henry C. Frick Educational Commission
  - Henry Clay Frick Community Hospital (Mount Pleasant, Pa.)
  - Henry Clay Frick Training School for Teachers; SEE Frick Training School for Teachers (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Heritage Broadcast Institute
  - Herr's Island (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Herron Avenue Presbyterian Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Herron Family
  - Highland House (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Highland Park (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Hiland Presbyterian Church (Ross, Pa.)
  - Hilary Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Hill City (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Hill District (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Hill District (Pittsburgh, Pa.). Community Council
  - Hill District Community Council; SEE Hill District (Pittsburgh, Pa.). Community Council
  - Hill House Association
  - Hillcrest United Presbyterian Church (Burgettstown, Pa.)
  - Hillel Academy of Pittsburgh
  - Hindu Americans; SEE East Indian Americans
  - Hispanic Americans- Pennsylvania
  - Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania
  - Hively Family
  - Holy Family Polish National Catholic Church (McKeesport, Pa.)
  - Holy Family Roman Catholic Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Holy Family School (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Holy Innocents Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Holy Name of the Blessed Virgin Mary Church (Donora, Pa.)
  - Holy Rosary Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Holy Sepulcher Church (Butler, Pa.)
  - Holy Spirit Roman Catholic Church (West Mifflin, Pa.)
  - Holy Trinity Lutheran Church (Jeannette, Pa.)
  - Holy Trinity Roman Catholic Church (Ambridge, Pa.)
  - Holy Trinity Roman Catholic Church (Beaver Falls, Pa.)
  - Holy Trinity Roman Catholic Church (Moon Run, Pa.)
  - Holy Trinity Roman Catholic Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Holy Trinity Serbian Eastern Orthodox Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Home for Crippled Children; SEE Rehabilitation Institute of Pittsburgh
  - Homestead (Pa.)
  - Homestead Strike, 1892
  - Homewood Cemetery Historical Fund (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Homewood-Brushton (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Homewood-Brushton Citizens Renewal Council
  - Homewood-Brushton Community Council
  - Homewood-Brushton Community Improvement Association
  - Homewood-Brushton Concerned Citizens
  - Homewood-Brushton Youth and Adult Kraal
  - Horner Family; SEE Daft Family
  - Hospital Council of Western Pennsylvania
  - Hospital Planning Association of Allegheny County (Pa.)
  - Hospital Service Association of Pittsburgh (Pa.)
  - Housing- Pennsylvania- Pittsburgh
  - Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh
  - Howes, Allan J.
  - Hungarian Americans- Pennsylvania
  - Hunger Action Coalition (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Hungry Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Hunt, Alfred M. (Alfred Mortimer), 1919-
  - Hussey Family
  - Hyeholde (Coraopolis Heights, Pa.)
- I
  - Illery, Alma
  - Immaculate Conception Roman Catholic Church (Carnegie, Pa.)
  - Immaculate Conception Roman Catholic Parish (Connellsville, Pa.)
  - Immaculate Heart of Mary Roman Catholic Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Immigrants; SEE [Place name]- Emigration and Immigration
  - Immigration; SEE [Place name]- Emigration and Immigration
  - Independent Order of Odd Fellows
  - Indians of North America- Pennsylvania
  - Industrial Development Company (New Kensington, Pa.)
  - International Samovar Club of Pittsburgh
  - International Theatre (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Irene Kaufmann Center of Squirrel Hill (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Irene Kaufmann Settlement (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Irish Americans- Pennsylvania
  - Iron City Mutual Life Insurance Company of Pennsylvania
  - Irvin Works; SEE Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation. Irvin Works
  - Italian Americans- Pennsylvania
- J
  - J. M. Gusky Orphanage and Home (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Japanese Americans- Pennsylvania
  - Jenkins Arcade (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Jewish Americans- Pennsylvania; SEE Jews- Pennsylvania
  - Jewish Community Center (Aliquippa, Pa.)
  - Jewish Community Center of Pittsburgh
  - Jewish Community Relations Council (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Jewish Family and Children's Service (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Jewish Healthcare Foundation of Pittsburgh
  - Jewish Home and Hospital for Aged (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Jewish Home for Aged (Pittsburgh, Pa.); SEE Jewish Home and Hospital for Aged (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Jewish War Veterans of the United States of America. Post 49 (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Jews- Pennsylvania
  - Job Advisory Service (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - John M. Roberts and Son Co.
  - Johnstown (Pa.)- Maps
  - Joint City-County Stadium Study Committee
  - Joint Committee on Service to New Immigrants
  - Jones, Mary; SEE Jones, Mother, 1843?-1930
  - Jones, Mother, 1843?-1930
  - Jones & Laughlin Steel Company- SEE Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation
  - Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation
  - Jones Family
  - Joy Manufacturing Company
  - Junior Chamber of Commerce of Pittsburgh
  - Junior League of Pittsburgh
  - Juvenile Court Aid Society (Allegheny County, Pa.)
  - Juvenile Court Association of Allegheny County
- K
  - KDKA (Radio Station: Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Kaufmann's Department Store. Program for Women in Business
  - Kaufmann's Program for Women in Business; SEE Kaufmann's Department Store. Program for Women in Business.
  - Kay Boys' Club
  - Kelly, Alexander
  - Kennywood Park (Pa.). American Slovak Day; SEE American Slovak Day (Kennywood Park (Pa.))
  - Kennywood Park (Pa.). Byzantine Catholic Day; SEE Byzantine Catholic Day (Kennywood Park (Pa.))
  - Kennywood Park (Pa.). Croatian Day; SEE Croatian Day (Kennywood Park (Pa.))
  - Kennywood Park (Pa.) Polish American Day; SEE Polish American Day (Kennywood Park (Pa.))
  - Kholos, Max
  - Kidd Drawn Steel Company
  - Kiwanis Club of Pittsburgh
  - Knights of Columbus. Chapter No. Five (Western Pennsylvania)
  - Knights of Equity. Court #9 (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Knights Templar (Masonic Order). Pittsburgh Commandery No. 1
  - Knoxville (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Koppers Company
  - Krul, Leopold J.
  - Kust, L. E.
- L
  - L. E. Smith Glass Company
  - LTV Corporation (formerly Jones and Laughlin)
  - Labor Day- Pennsylvania- Pittsburgh
  - Lake Erie and Ohio River Canal (Proposed)
  - Lambda Foundation
  - Land Use- Pennsylvania
  - Laotian Americans- Pennsylvania
  - Latvian Americans- Pennsylvania
  - Lauder Family
  - Laughlin Children's Center; SEE Mary and Alexander Laughlin Children's Center (Sewickley, Pa.)
  - Laughlin Family
  - Laurel Highlands Conservation & Development Project
  - Lawrenceville (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Lawrenceville Historical Society (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Le Mont (Restaurant: Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Leadership Pittsburgh, 1997-1999
  - League of Gay and Lesbian Voters (Pa.)
  - League of Women Voters (Allegheny County, Pa.)
  - Legal Aid Society of Pittsburgh
  - Legionville (Pa.)
  - Leishman Family
  - Lett, Harold A.
  - Levinson Steel Company
  - Lewis, Charles F.
  - Lewis, Oliver and Phillips Co.
  - Lewis, Oliver and Phillips Co.; SEE ALSO Phillips Mine Supply Co.
  - Liberation People's Press (Pa.)
  - Liberty Tunnels (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Linder, Benjamin
  - Lions Club of Swissvale (Pa.)
  - Lithuanian Americans- Pennsylvania
  - Lloyd Family
  - Local Initiatives Support Corporation
  - Lockwood Family
  - Lockwood Family; SEE ALSO Daft Family
  - Louise Child Care Center (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Lutheran Service Society of Western Pennsylvania
- M
  - MPC Corporation
  - McCandless (Pa.)
  - McCormick Family
  - McDowell, Arthur G.
  - Machsikei Hadas Congregation; SEE Congregation Machsikei Hadas (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - McKees Rocks (Pa.)
  - McKeesport Intercultural Council
  - Mackintosh Family
  - Madoff, Michelle
  - Madonna Del Castello Roman Catholic Church (Swissvale, Pa.)
  - Magee Women's Hospital (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Magee Women's Hospital (Pittsburgh, Pa.). Twenty-Five Club
  - Maguire, Charles B. (Charles Bonaventure), 1770?-1833
  - Mail-Well Envelope Company
  - Manchester Citizens Corporation
  - Mansfield & Co., Ltd. (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Manufacturing Industries- Pennsylvania- Pittsburgh- History
  - Maps- Bibliography
  - Marquette Canoe Club (Oakmont, Pa.)
  - Mary and Alexander Laughlin Children's Center (Sewickley, Pa.)
  - Mason, Louis
  - Mayor's Code...; SEE Pittsburgh (Pa.). Mayor's Code...
  - Mayor's Committee...; SEE Pittsburgh (Pa.). Mayor's Committee...
  - Mayor's Task Force...; SEE Pittsburgh (Pa.). Mayor's Task Force...
  - Mayview State Hospital (Mayview, Pa.)
  - Mc; FILED AS Mac
  - Mellon Family
  - Mellon Institute
  - Mellon National Bank and Trust Company
  - Mental Health Association of Butler County
  - Mental Health Center (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Mesta Machine Co.
  - Metcalf Family
  - Methodist Episcopal Church Annual Conference (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Metropolitan Citizens Organization (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Metropolitan Community Church of Pittsburgh
  - Militant Forum
  - Miller Family
  - Miller, Oliver
  - Mizrachi Organization of America. Pittsburgh District
  - Mock, Jerrie
  - Mon-Valley Unemployed Committee
  - Monastery of the Holy Transfiguration; SEE Orthodox Monastery of the Holy Transfiguration (Elwood City, Pa.)
  - Monday Luncheon Club (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Monessen (Pa.)
  - Monongahela Incline Plane (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Monongahela River Buffs Association
  - Monroeville (Pa.)
  - Monsour Medical Foundation
  - Montefiore Hospital (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Montours Presbyterian Church (Robinson Township, Allegheny County, Pa.)
  - Moore, Charles C. (Charles Core)
  - Morningside (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Morrow Family
  - Mother of Good Counsel Roman Catholic Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Mother of Sorrows Roman Catholic Church (McKees Rocks, Pa.)
  - Mothers' Assistance Fund (Allegheny County, Pa.)
  - Mount Lebanon (Pa.)
  - Mount Lebanon Citizens for Community Relations
  - Mount Lebanon United Methodist Church (Mount Lebanon, Pa.)
  - Mount Oliver (Pa.)
  - Mount Pleasant (Westmoreland County, Pa.: Township)
  - Mount St. Peter's Roman Catholic Church (New Kensington, Pa.)
  - Mount Washington Academy of Dance
  - Mount Washington German Building and Loan Association
  - Mueller, Sebastian, 1860-1952
  - Munroe Family
  - Murray, Philip, 1886-1952
  - Mushroom Family
  - Mystery Lovers Bookshop
- N
  - National Association for Women Deans, Administrators & Counselors
  - National Council of Jewish Women. Pittsburgh Section; SEE ALSO Council of Jewish Women (U.S.). Greater Pittsburgh Section
  - National Council of Negro Women, Region II
  - National Slovak Society of the United States of America
  - National Steel Corporation
  - Native Americans; SEE Indians of North America
  - Negro Educational Emergency Drive
  - NeighborFair Pittsburgh Inc.
  - Neighborhood Mini-Code Housing Committee (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Neighborhoods for Living Center (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Netting, M. Graham
  - Network to Save the Mon/Ohio Valley Union Men and Women
  - Neville Island Presbyterian Church (Neville Island, Pa.)
  - New Castle (Pa.)
  - New Democratic Coalition of Pennsylvania
  - New Light Congregation (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Nickelodeon (Motion Picture Theater: Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Nimick Family
  - Nine Mile Run (Pa.)
  - North Boroughs Council Republican Women; SEE Pennsylvania Council of Republican Women. North Boroughs Council
  - North Boroughs Lions Club
  - North Branch United Presbyterian Church (Monaca, Pa.)
  - North Side (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - North Side Community Council (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
- O
  - O'Have Israel Congregation; SEE Congregation O'Have Israel (Brownsville, Pa.)
  - Oakdale Military Installation (Pa.)
  - Oakland (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Oakland Baptist Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Oakland Community Council (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Oakland Cooperative Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Oakland Corporation (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Oakland Savings and Trust Company
  - Oakland Women's Center (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Obel Jacob Congregation (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Obernauer & Co.
  - Obie Construction Co.
  - Ohav Shalom Congregation; SEE Temple Ohav Shalom (Allison Park, Pa.)
  - Ohio Valley General Hospital
  - Old Congruity Presbyterian Church (Westmoreland County, Pa.)
  - Older Adults Resource Service
  - Oliver Family
  - Opportunities Industrialization Center (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Organization of Chinese Americans. Pittsburgh Chapter; SEE Organization of Chinese Americans. Tri-State Chapter
  - Organization of Chinese Americans. Tri-State Chapter
  - Orthodox Church in America. Archdiocese of Pittsburgh and West Virginia
  - Orthodox Monastery of the Holy Transfiguration (Elwood City, Pa.)
  - Orthodoxos Ekklesia tes Hellados- Pennsylvania- Pittsburgh
  - Orton, Edward, 1863-1932
  - Our Lady Help of Christians Roman Catholic Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Our Lady of Consolation Roman Catholic Church (Nemacolin, Pa.)
  - Our Lady of Czestochowa Roman Catholic Church (New Castle, Pa.)
  - Our Lady of Fatima Chapel (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Our Lady of Grace Roman Catholic Church (Scott Township, Allegheny County, Pa.)
  - Our Lady of Loreto Roman Catholic Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Our Lady of Peace Roman Catholic Church (Conway, Pa.)
  - Our Lady of the Angels Roman Catholic Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Our Lady of the Miraculous Medal Roman Catholic Church (Meadow Lands, Pa.)
  - Our Lady of the Most Blessed Sacrament Roman Catholic Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Our Lady of Victory Roman Catholic Church (Harwick, Pa.)
  - Our Lady Queen of Peace Roman Catholic Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Ozanam Cultural Center (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
- P
  - P-FLAG Pittsburgh; SEE Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays. Pittsburgh Chapter
  - PPG Industries
  - Pacific Islander Americans- Pennsylvania
  - Page Family; SEE Lockwood Family
  - Pakistani Americans- Pennsylvania
  - Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays. Pittsburgh Chapter
  - Park Baptist Church (McKeesport, Pa.)
  - Park Family
  - Park Schenley (Restaurant: Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Parkin Family
  - Parks- Pennsylvania- Pittsburgh
  - Parkway Jewish Center Shaar Ha-Shamayim (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Passionist Nuns of Our Lady of Sorrows
  - Payne Chapel African Methodist Episcopal Church (Duquesne, Pa.)
  - Peabody High School (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Peacock Family
  - Penn (Allegheny County, Pa.: Township)
  - Penn Circle Community High School (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Penn Township; SEE Penn (Allegheny County, Pa.: Township)
  - Pennsylvania. County Court (Allegheny County)
  - Pennsylvania. Court of Common Pleas (Allegheny County). Juvenile Section
  - Pennsylvania. Department of Environmental Protection
  - Pennsylvania Abortion Coalition
  - Pennsylvania Alliance for Jobs and Energy
  - Pennsylvania Association for Retarded Children. Allegheny County Chapter
  - Pennsylvania Association for the Blind. Pittsburgh Branch
  - Pennsylvania Council of Republican Women. North Boroughs Council
  - Pennsylvania Elected Women's Association. Allegheny County Chapter
  - Pennsylvania Federation of Temple Sisterhoods
  - Pennsylvania Insurance Company of Pittsburgh
  - Pennsylvania Mason Juvenile Court Institute
  - Pennsylvania Peace Links
  - Pennsylvania Railroad
  - Pennsylvania Smelting Company
  - Pennsylvania, Southwest
  - Pennsylvania Station Restaurant (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Perry Hilltop Action Council; SEE Perry Hilltop Citizens' Council
  - Perry Hilltop Citizens' Council
  - Persad Center, Inc.
  - Phi Delta Kappa. Three Rivers Chapter 14
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity. Pittsburgh Alumni Club
  - Philatelic Society of Pittsburgh
  - Phillips Family
  - Phillips Mine Supply Co.
  - Phillips Mine Supply Co.; SEE ALSO Lewis, Oliver and Phillips Co.
  - Phipps Family
  - Pine (Allegheny County, Pa.: Township)
  - Pine Creek Presbyterian Church (Fox Chapel, Pa.)
  - Pioneer Women (Organization: U.S.). Pittsburgh Council
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- Biography
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- Buildings, structures, etc.
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- Centennial celebrations, etc.
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- Emigration and Immigration
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- Floods
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- History- 19th Century
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- In Literature
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- Lithographs
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- Maps
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- Newspapers
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.)- Population
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Better Traffic Committee
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Board of Public Education; SEE Pittsburgh Board of Public Education (Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Building Code; SEE Building laws- Pennsylvania- Pittsburgh
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Bureau of Building Inspection; SEE Pittsburgh (Pa.). Department of Public Safety. Bureau of Building Inspection
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Bureau of Fire; SEE Pittsburgh (Pa.). Fire Department
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Bureau of Recreational Activities
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Bureau of Smoke Regulation
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). City Planning Commission
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Civil Service Commission
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Commission on Human Relations
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Commission on Human Relations. Research Advisory Committee
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Department of Emergency Medical Services
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Department of City Development
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Department of City Planning
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Department of City Planning. Social Planning Advisory Committee
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Department of Housing
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Department of Parks and Recreation
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Department of Public Safety. Bureau of Building Inspection
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Department of Public Welfare
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Department of Public Works
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Fire Department
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Government Study Commission
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Historic Review Commission
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Housing Authority; SEE Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Mayor
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Mayor's Code Enforcement Advisory Committee
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Mayor's Committee on Human Resources
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Mayor's Task Force on Racial Disorder
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Mayor's Task Force on Women in Renaissance II
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Police Research Commission
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). School Board; SEE Pittsburgh Board of Public Education (Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). School District; SEE Pittsburgh School District (Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh (Pa.). Zoning Ordinance; SEE Zoning law- Pennsylvania- Pittsburgh
  - Pittsburgh Action Against Rape, Inc.
  - Pittsburgh Advisory Committee on Housing and Community Development
  - Pittsburgh Agreement on Czechoslovakia (1918); SEE Czecho-Slovak Pact (Pittsburgh, Pa.: May 30, 1918)
  - Pittsburgh Alliance for Safer Streets
  - Pittsburgh and Allegheny Free Kindergarten Association; SEE Pittsburgh Kindergarten Association
  - Pittsburgh and Allegheny Milk and Ice Association
  - Pittsburgh Area Religion and Race Council
  - Pittsburgh Association for the Advancement of Women
  - Pittsburgh Association for the Improvement of the Poor
  - Pittsburgh Association for the Relief of the Poor
  - Pittsburgh Association of Credit Men
  - Pittsburgh Baptist Association
  - Pittsburgh Better Traffic Committee; SEE Pittsburgh (Pa.). Better Traffic Committee
  - Pittsburgh Bibliophiles (Society)
  - Pittsburgh Bicentennial Commission (Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh Black Women's Health Network
  - Pittsburgh Board of Public Education (Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh Board of Trade; SEE Board of Trade of Pittsburgh (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh Business and Professional Women's Club; SEE Business and Professional Women's Club of Pittsburgh, Pa.
  - Pittsburgh Central High School (Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce; SEE Chamber of Commerce of Pittsburgh
  - Pittsburgh Chess Club
  - Pittsburgh Child Guidance Center
  - Pittsburgh City Home and Hospitals (Mayview, Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh City Planning Commission; SEE Pittsburgh (Pa.). City Planning Commission
  - Pittsburgh Civic Commission
  - Pittsburgh Clean City Committee, Inc.
  - Pittsburgh Club
  - Pittsburgh Coalition for Justice, Peace and New Priorities
  - Pittsburgh Commission on Human Relations; SEE Pittsburgh (Pa.). Commission on Human Relations
  - Pittsburgh Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy
  - Pittsburgh Community Council
  - Pittsburgh Convention & Visitors Bureau
  - Pittsburgh Council for International Visitors
  - Pittsburgh Council on Adult Education; SEE Greater Pittsburgh Council on Adult Education
  - Pittsburgh Council on Intercultural Education
  - Pittsburgh Council on Public Education
  - Pittsburgh Diagnostic Clinic
  - Pittsburgh Eisteddfod Association
  - Pittsburgh Electric Railway Club
  - Pittsburgh Ethnic Coalition
  - Pittsburgh Experiment
  - Pittsburgh Florence Crittenton Home; SEE Florence Crittenton Home (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh Folk Festival
  - Pittsburgh Free Clinic
  - Pittsburgh Girls' Conference
  - Pittsburgh Golf Club
  - Pittsburgh Habonim
  - Pittsburgh Hearing Society, Inc.
  - Pittsburgh Historic Review Commission; SEE Pittsburgh (Pa.). Historic Review Commission
  - Pittsburgh History & Landmarks Foundation
  - Pittsburgh Hockey Club
  - Pittsburgh Housing Association
  - Pittsburgh Housing Authority; SEE Housing Authority of the City of Pittsburgh
  - Pittsburgh Industrial Development Commission
  - Pittsburgh Industrial Development Council
  - Pittsburgh Institute of Lifelong Learning
  - Pittsburgh International Airport
  - Pittsburgh International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival
  - Pittsburgh Jaycees; SEE Junior Chamber of Commerce of Pittsburgh
  - Pittsburgh Kindergarten Association
  - Pittsburgh League for the Hard of Hearing, Inc.
  - Pittsburgh Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Pride Celebration
  - Pittsburgh Lord Marley Committee
  - Pittsburgh Maternal Health Center
  - Pittsburgh Model Cities Commission
  - Pittsburgh Monthly Meeting of the Religious Society of Friends (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh Neighborhood Alliance
  - Pittsburgh Orchestra Association
  - Pittsburgh Pact (1918); SEE Czecho-Slovak Pact (Pittsburgh, Pa.: May 30, 1918)
  - Pittsburgh Parks Conservancy
  - Pittsburgh Partnership
  - Pittsburgh Peace Coalition
  - Pittsburgh Pirates (Baseball team)
  - Pittsburgh Presbytery; SEE United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. Presbytery of Pittsburgh
  - Pittsburgh Psychoanalytic Center, Inc.
  - Pittsburgh Psychoanalytic Institute
  - Pittsburgh Radical Women's Union
  - Pittsburgh Regional Planning Association
  - Pittsburgh School District (Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh Stock Exchange
  - Pittsburgh Student Committee for Soviet Jewry
  - Pittsburgh Symphony Society
  - Pittsburgh Teachers' Institute
  - Pittsburgh Teachers' Training School; SEE Frick Training School for Teachers (Pittsburgh, Pa.)
  - Pittsburgh Theological Seminary
  - Pittsburgh Training School for Teachers; SEE Frick Training School for Teachers (Pittsburgh, Pa.)